I want to welcome y'all I guess we have
我想欢迎你们，我想我们有
we already have a lot of these thank you
我们已经有很多这样的谢谢
for for joining and I'm going to talk
加入，我要谈谈
about shifting security from right to
关于将安全性从权利转移到权利
left the first thing is what does that
剩下的第一件事是什么
mean shifting security from right to
意味着将安全从权利转移到
left
剩下
well if you look from a security
好吧，如果您从证券看
perspective then security is most of the
角度来看，安全是最重要的
time it's on the right pot that what we
时间是在正确的锅上，
what mean by bad is if you see a
不好的意思是如果您看到一个
timeline for left to right then on the
从左到右然后在
right path you have your CI system or
您拥有CI系统的正确路径，或者
well just before you go into production
就在您投产之前
we have that security team in place that
我们有一个安全团队
checks your stuff most of the time they
他们大多数时候会检查您的东西
are the only security and force so you
是唯一的安全和力量，所以您
have well we think that by moving
好吧，我们认为通过移动
security to the left so to the
左侧的安全性
developers focus that will be much much
开发人员关注的重点是
more nicer because actually what we're
更好，因为实际上我们是
talking about is the work there seconds
谈论那里的工作是几秒钟
and personally I don't know about you
我个人不了解你
too sure but I hate the word exdeath
太确定了，但我讨厌亡灵这个词
checkups it sounds it sounds like sounds
体检听起来像听起来
like my grandfather that wants to talk
就像我想说话的祖父
with the cool kids and and we had this
和很酷的孩子一起，我们有了这个
this thing with developer and operations
这件事与开发人员和运营有关
and that sounded kind of okay with their
听起来他们的还行
vote so now we have this sack in the
投票，所以现在我们有这个麻袋
middle which tends like yes security is
倾向于是安全的中间是
everywhere and we have to do it
到处都有，我们必须这样做
everywhere although I may not like the
到处都是，尽管我可能不喜欢
word def setups because well I don't
word def设置，因为我不知道
think it's pretty I do agree with the
认为我确实同意
mindset of it because we need to be
的心态，因为我们需要
aware of security I think from every
我从每个人那里都意识到安全性
angle within our development cycle and
在我们的开发周期中的角度
thinking about that let me first
考虑一下，让我先
introduce myself because well people may
自我介绍，因为好人可能
not know me I'm Brian I'm working for as
不认识我，我是Brian，我为
a developer at forget for a sneak
忘记了的开发人员
there's so now you know company I'm
所以现在你知道我是公司
based in Holland I work also work for
我在荷兰工作，也为
the huge oak that's a little jus pop it
巨大的橡木有点像
over there and I'm co-lead for the
在那边，我共同领导
secure developer which is a community
安全的社区开发人员
and online community we run their focus
和在线社区，我们将重点放在
is on secure development from the
正在从
developer focus we worked together with
我们与之合作的开发者关注重点
also all sorts of companies over there
那里的各种各样的公司
so if you
所以如果你
feel like this is something you want you
觉得这是你想要的东西
put more attention in feel free to join
随时加入更多关注
over there but going back to the two
在那边，然后回到两个
deaths Eccles what are we what are we
死亡传世我们是什么我们是什么
trying to do with the deaf setups well
试图很好地处理聋人的设置
well it's actually the problem about
嗯，这实际上是关于
this cycle what is the problem that we
这个周期是什么问题，我们
want to solve I think for the people
想解决我想为人民
that work in say the banking environment
可以说银行环境
or government agencies they probably
或他们可能是政府机构
know that a decade ago or even a few
知道十年前甚至几十年
years ago they were deploying maybe
多年前他们正在部署
twice a year three times a year and what
一年两次一年三次
you see now is that we are speeding up
您现在看到的是我们正在加速
that delivery everybody want to speed up
每个人都希望加快交货速度
the delivery because we want to be ahead
交货，因为我们想领先
of our competitors we want to have this
我们的竞争对手中，我们希望拥有这个
new business value we want to create it
我们想要创造新的商业价值
in small pieces in smaller iterations
在较小的迭代中分成小块
and when it's done we want to do some
当完成后，我们想做一些
sort of continuous integration and
不断的整合和
continuous delivery but by that it means
连续交付，但这意味着
that now and well you can say that
现在，那么你可以说
they're only focusing on creating his
他们只专注于创造他的
stuff and that's good that's a good
东西，那很好，那很好
thing I mean business value is the
我的意思是业务价值是
reason why you survive as a company or
您作为公司生存的原因或
why you make money as the company but
为什么你作为公司赚钱，但是
the other part is more like okay if it's
另一部分更像是可以
not if it's not going wrong nothing is
如果没有出错，那就不是
happening right and we do not have that
正确的事情，我们没有那个
much of a focus on security because we
我们非常注重安全性，因为我们
need to speed up these things so if we
需要加快这些事情，所以如果我们
have a lack of focus on security during
缺乏对安全性的关注
that that lifecycle it might mean that
那生命周期可能意味着
we do look into security but catch these
我们确实调查了安全性，但抓住了这些
things way too late or not at all and
事情太迟了或根本没有
that's because we're still doing living
那是因为我们还在生活
in a sword amount of siloed security
剑灵般的安全感
expertise all security teams most times
大部分时间都向所有安全团队提供专业知识
are at the end of the line the
在行的结尾
gatekeeper that says stop you gotta go
看门人说停止你要走
to production because well you do have a
投入生产，因为您确实有一个
vulnerability on the other side we want
我们想要的另一方面
to they want to do penetration testing
他们想做渗透测试
they want to do audits or whatever and
他们想进行审核或其他
that takes a while it takes a couple of
需要一些时间
days maybe a week or maybe even more and
几天，也许一周或更长时间，
I deploy now two times a day for
我现在每天部署两次
instance because well we do this cool
实例，因为我们做得很酷
micro service kind of thing and swallow
微服务那种东西和吞
durations there we go and up the
持续的时间我们去了
mountain and
山和
by the time they tested my stuff I'm
当他们测试我的东西时，我
probably like 10 iterations away from
大概距离10次迭代
that but the most important thing is if
但最重要的是
we are not doing the security or not to
我们不做安全或不做
do security in a proper way I customer
以正确的方式为客户提供安全保障
data could be compromised and that's
数据可能会被泄露，这就是
something we all do not want to happen
我们都不想发生的事情
we have this gdpr law in place here in
我们在这里制定了该gdpr法律
Europe but in general things like PII
欧洲，但总的来说像PII
data just lying around for grabs is not
只是为了获取数据而已
a good thing so how bad is that
好东西，那有多糟
situation well we've got a couple of
情况很好，我们有几个
times at the Nissan and this always is
时代在日产，这总是
the question I ask the people is have
我问人民的问题是
you ever heard of Equifax and a lot of
您曾经听说过Equifax和很多
people have heard of Equifax well
人们都听说过Equifax
because of these things in the newspaper
因为报纸上的这些东西
or new sites and if I ask the people did
或新网站，如果我问人们做了
you know about Equifax like three years
你知道三年的Equifax
ago or two to have years ago most of
一两年前有很多
them didn't so you could say this is
他们没有，所以你可以说这是
good marketing but I disagree with that
良好的行销能力，但我不同意
this is my business might be like one
这可能是我的事
big problem they do know your name but
大问题他们确实知道您的名字，但是
what happened with Equifax is that
Equifax发生的是
Equifax was using and I'm using this
Equifax正在使用，而我正在使用
because as well it's not the only
因为它也不是唯一
company that is breached but this is the
被破坏的公司，但这是
one that is breached because they were
被违反的原因之一是
using a dependency upon she struts
使用对她的依赖
dependency that was outdated and it
过时的依赖关系
wasn't just outdated it in their
不只是在他们的过时了
specific version they were using a
他们使用的特定版本
Apache struts had a vulnerability an ADD
Apache Struts有一个ADD漏洞
for ability at a certain time was found
发现某时间的能力
was disclosed was documented and there
被公开记录在案
was already a fix for it but if you do
已经解决了，但是如果您这样做
not know that you have it or you do not
不知道你有没有
scan properly or you do not get warned
扫描正确，否则您不会收到警告
by somebody that you're using that one
被某人使用的那个
you might end up having this one in
你可能最终拥有这个
production way too long at the end 143
143年末生产方式过长
million users accounts or data buy one
百万用户帐户或数据购买一个
on 443 people were were breached or
有443人被破坏或
people's stuff were on the street so
人们的东西在街上，所以
that means that a lot of people's into
这意味着很多人
the data or important data that you do
您所做的数据或重要数据
not want to get out was that on the
不想出去的是
street and again is there something like
街上又有类似的东西
bat marketing well I guess so but if we
蝙蝠营销很好，我想是的，但是如果我们
point that back to our thing I mean most
指出我的意思是最重要的
of us probably are developers and if we
我们当中可能是开发人员，如果我们
look at development and we look at your
看发展，我们看你
application then we just see your
应用程序，那么我们只会看到您的
application as this then we can say the
这样的应用程序，那么我们可以说
amount of code you produce in that
您在其中产生的代码量
application make probably if it is
应用程序可能是
because for all the things we do but we
因为我们所做的一切，但我们
only want to focus on the real business
只想专注于真实业务
logic the things that do make a
逻辑做的事情使
difference and not all the boilerplate
差异，而不是所有样板
stuff like creating crud repositories
诸如创建原始存储库之类的东西
creating rest repositories making sure
创建剩余存储库，确保
that all the plumbing is done we heavily
我们完成了所有的管道工程
depend on frameworks libraries and all
取决于框架库和所有
sorts of third library a Third Point
各种第三图书馆的第三点
library of stuff most of it is open
资料库大部分是开放的
source and we blindly use it and is that
源，我们盲目地使用它，那是
good or not well I would say it's not a
好还是不好，我会说这不是一个
problem that use open source we support
使用我们支持的开源问题
open source I'm a big fan of open source
开源我是开源的忠实粉丝
but we have to be sure that open source
但是我们必须确保开源
is just open source of error there are a
只是错误的开放源而已
couple maintainers on it or maybe a lot
几个维护者，也许很多
of maintenance on it but if something
维修，但如果有的话
slips in it might be a problem for a
滑倒可能是一个问题
whole lot of people because well it's
很多人，因为这是
being used quite widely so just an
被广泛使用，因此
overview I have a serverless example
概述我有一个无服务器的示例
over here and you don't have to look at
在这里，你不必看
the code because well I won't say it's
代码，因为我不会说
that pretty but it's 19 lines of code it
很漂亮，但是它是19行代码
has a few dependencies well two direct
有一些依赖关系，两个直接
dependencies and as we know every
依赖关系，众所周知
dependency every major dependency have
每个主要依赖都有
transitive dependencies so dependencies
传递性依存关系
depend on dependencies and depending on
依赖于依赖和依赖
other dependencies in total we have 19
我们总共有19个其他依赖项
dependencies well just take a second you
依赖关系好一点
might and think how many lines of code
可能会想到多少行代码
we actually put into production by just
我们实际上只是通过
this small service example with this two
这两个的小服务示例
direct dependencies I hope you made a
直接依赖我希望你做了
guess in inside of your mind
在你的内心猜测
it's like almost two hundred thousand
差不多二十万
lines of code so you see a lot of the
代码行，因此您会看到很多
code lines of code you put into
您放入的代码行
production are not yours second one
生产不是你的第二个
22 lines of code pretty neat application
22行代码非常简洁的应用程序
because spring service and it has five
因为春季服务，它有五个
direct dependencies these five direct
直接依赖这五个直接
dependencies results in 54 dependencies
依赖导致54个依赖
in total well you saw how much lines of
总共，您看到了多少行
code we put in production and we know
我们投入生产的代码，我们知道
that while spring does a lot for you in
虽然春天对你有很大帮助
this in our Java ecosystem so how are
这在我们的Java生态系统中如何
how many lines of code do you think
您认为多少行代码
these 22 222 lines of code bring you in
这22222行代码将您带入
you you will bring in production almost
您几乎可以带来生产
half a million so you see that we depend
五百万，所以你看到我们依靠
a lot on other people's stuff and use it
很多别人的东西，并使用它
and that is good because we do not want
那很好，因为我们不想
to do that might work but that much work
做到这一点可能会奏效，但要做很多工作
on boilerplate and if it's done already
在样板上，如果已经完成
and it's done properly why not use it
正确完成了为什么不使用它
right on the other hand this open source
另一方面，这个开源
usage has exploded to last a couple of
用法爆炸了持续数次
years well not last couple years I think
好几年不是最近几年
over a lot the last decade and if this
在过去十年中，如果这
or if there if the usage of open source
还是如果使用开源
is exploded then we'll see that if we
爆炸了，那么我们会看到，如果我们
have one foreigner ability in a major
在专业中只有一种外国人的能力
package that then we will see that many
包，那么我们将看到很多
companies many many programs many
公司很多很多程序很多
applications are vulnerable and
应用程序容易受到攻击
attackers will get into different
攻击者将陷入不同
abilities and try them out randomly
能力并随机尝试
because Equifax for instance wasn't
因为例如Equifax不是
particularly targeted now Equifax was
现在特别针对的是Equifax
just well that luck I would say people
好吧，我会说人
try that the exploit and found out that
尝试利用该漏洞，并发现
with this company they were having that
在这家公司，他们有
old struts library and they could create
旧的struts库，他们可以创建
maybe they were in there for months and
也许他们在那里呆了几个月，
silently looking into the systems and
静静地看着系统，
found out what they're having there over
找出他们在那边有什么
there
那里
so there is a risk of open source not
因此存在开源风险
that you shouldn't use your open source
你不应该使用开源
again but you we should be aware of the
再次，但您应该注意
fact that because of the wide adoption
事实上，由于被广泛采用
of it there are some risk if you if we
如果您有任何风险，如果我们
look at for instance how many packages
看例如多少包
there are in the ecosystem and how many
生态系统中有多少
packages how many the Tokyo indexed
打包东京索引的数量
packages were groped last year let me
去年摸索了包装让我
see that
看到
well an PM is the clear winner and it's
PM显然是赢家，这是
easy to pick on JavaScript but because
易于选择JavaScript，但是因为
NPM has a package for everything I know
NPM提供了我所知道的所有内容的软件包
to packet or three or four packages for
打包或三个或四个包裹
everything but if we look at a line that
一切，但如果我们看一条线，
maven central has because well maybe in
Maven Central有，因为也许在
central is still the largest one that
中央仍然是最大的
supplies packages for you within our
在我们内部为您提供包裹
Java ecosystem they see that this line
他们看到Java生态系统这一行
is very steep as well and if we look at
也非常陡峭，如果我们看一下
how many new vulnerabilities last year
去年有多少新漏洞
or the last couple of years were
或最近几年是
introduced we in the Java ecosystem are
介绍我们在Java生态系统中
the clear winner and that's something we
明确的赢家，这就是我们
shouldn't be proud of however if we look
如果我们看的话不应该为此感到骄傲
at the premises then you see that more
在这里，你会看到更多
or less not the poor for us for the Java
或更少不是我们的Java穷人
ecosystem but also for NPM for instance
生态系统，例如NPM
it's not so much the dependency we
与其说是依赖，不如说是
actually download but the dependencies
实际下载但依赖项
underneath if you well if you in for
如果你在下面，如果你很好
instance you spring and spring makes use
你春天和春天利用的实例
of a lot of upper dependencies well
很多上层依赖
because marshaling for instance make
因为例如封送处理
sure that there are repositories
确保有存储库
available that drivers can run so we
驱动程序可以运行的可用状态，因此我们
depend on a lot of things under the hood
取决于很多事情
that we may not know and most of these
我们可能不知道的大多数
flaws and most of the problems are in
缺陷和大多数问题都在
the indirect appendices and not so much
间接附录，没有那么多
in direct dependencies and if we ask
直接依赖，如果我们问
these maintain Asst like ok how
这些保持好起来如何
confident are you in your owns in your
你对自己有信心吗
own security knowledge well only 30%
拥有30％的安全知识
things there have high their scale of of
那里的东西规模很高
security knowledge is quite high and 63
安全知识很高，并且63
things its well ok if and how much do we
事情还好吧，如果我们以及多少钱
lean on that ok age do we do we do we
依靠那个好的年龄，我们做我们做我们
trusted that that's blindly again
相信那又是盲目的
but if we look at the other way around
但是如果我们换个角度来看
we are creating new software as
我们正在创建新软件
developers right and who is responsible
开发者权利和责任人
for security
为了安全
well at least 89% of the the people we
我们至少有89％的人
interviewed and this is done by jury
接受采访，由陪审团完成
with a will a large survey that ended up
最终完成了一项大规模调查
in a report called the state of open
在一份称为开放状态的报告中
social security you can download it from
您可以从中下载社会保障
our website but and we and in this
我们的网站，但我们和在此
survey we talked to a lot of open-source
我们与很多开源聊天的调查
maintainers and application developers
维护人员和应用程序开发人员
in general and by that in that survey
总的来说，在那个调查中
the result was that people think that
结果是人们认为
developers should at least have 81% of
开发人员至少应拥有81％
the people that were interviewed that
被采访的人
say that at least 89 or that developer
说至少89或那个开发商
should have a lot of responsibility
应该承担很多责任
if it comes to security and well you may
如果涉及安全性，那么您可能会
see that it's more than 100 percent
看到它超过100％
that's true because you can have shared
没错，因为您可以分享
responsibility most people think that
大多数人认为责任
it's developers and operations or
是开发人员和运营部门，还是
developers and the security team but you
开发人员和安全团队，但是您
see that we have to do something as a
看到我们必须做一些
developer and not just making a new
开发人员，而不仅仅是制作一个新的
shiny team things so if we ask people
团队合作的亮点，如果我们问别人
how to how do they find out about any
他们如何找到任何东西
vulnerability 27% probably won't or a
27％的漏洞可能不会或
lot of people just randomly scanned the
很多人只是随机扫​​描
sealy database and it's quite
sealy数据库，相当
frightening
吓人的
so say once the dependency is when once
所以说一次依赖是一次
the vulnerability is found disclose
该漏洞被发现泄露
documented and it's reported back to the
记录下来，并报告给
e to the suti owner to the to the people
e给suti所有者给人民
that maintain that package it's probably
维持那个包裹
been it gets fixed very well but how
修复得很好吗
many days in general does it take to get
一般需要几天的时间
such a thing fixed what do you think
这样的事情解决了你的想法
it's in days
在几天之内
and it's about sixteen days so that's
大约是16天，所以
not very long so it means once a
不太长，所以意味着一次
vulnerability is there people are very
那里的人很脆弱
keen on fixing the things and getting
热衷于修理东西并得到
out new packages but say the other way
出新的包裹，但换句话说
around say something is in production
周围说什么东西正在生产
and you leave it over there and it made
然后把它放在那边
might be might be not vulnerable at the
可能在当时可能并不脆弱
point you put into production how many
点你投产多少
days does it take for a funder ability
资金能力需要几天的时间
to be disclosed and to be documented in
在以下文件中公开和记录
general and this one is not in days
一般，这不是几天
this one is shockingly in years it's
这是令人震惊的几年
about two and a half years in general so
一般大约两年半左右
that means if we put in something that
这意味着如果我们放一些东西
is cool now and works now people will
现在很酷，现在可以工作了
try to dig into it and after a certain
尝试深入研究，并确定
amount of time they will find fun
他们会找到乐趣的时间
rapidity said it's not if you if the
速度说不是如果你
package is vulnerable to spending the
一揽子计划很容易支出
picture Bev ibex is fundable miles of
图片Bev ibex可用于
Sun and the same thing helps for things
太阳和同一件事对事物有帮助
like docker we're Dockett we're using
像docker我们是Dockett我们正在使用
docker nowadays heavily but if we look
码头工人如今沉重，但如果我们看
at for instance the docker images that
例如在docker镜像中
you can and that you can just download
你可以而且你可以下载
from docker hub then we see that even
从docker hub上，我们甚至看到
the the images that are from well their
来自他们的图像
own suppliers so the the note image if
自己的供应商，因此注释图片如果
you just download the the the real note
您只需下载真正的笔记
image from docker up you get that this
来自码头工人的图像，你得到这个
scan is done in somewhere and much you
扫描是在某个地方完成的
can over 500 funder abilities and these
可以提供超过500个资助者的能力，这些
vulnerabilities can almost all be traced
几乎可以追踪所有漏洞
back to the base image and that's that's
回到基本图片，就是这样
hard because I knowed as itself des is
很难，因为我知道des是
not it's not vulnerable but it's based
不是不是脆弱，而是基于
on an image on well a full-blown Debian
在成熟的Debian上的图像上
image that might bring all these
可能带来所有这些的图像
vulnerabilities with them and it had
与他们的漏洞，它有
this D and these are all d well well
这个D，这些都很好
these are the time most downloaded paper
这些是下载次数最多的时间
packages at that at that time so what I
当时的包裹，所以我
said it was March or something so
说是三月左右
we know that that most vulnerabilities
我们知道大多数漏洞
for docker on in any open source or any
适用于任何开源或任何形式的docker
operating system layer and if we ask
操作系统层，如果我们问
people do you scan for it do you do you
人们扫描它吗？
how do you know about it well a lot of
你怎么知道的很多
people just do not find out and I think
人们只是不知道，我认为
that's very the same thing is if we put
这是完全一样的，如果我们把
this thing into deployment and we just
这个东西部署了，我们只是
leave it over there a lot of people will
把它留在那边很多人会
not ever find out if they have a
从来没有发现他们是否有
vulnerability and again it doesn't stop
漏洞，它并没有停止
at the point you put into production but
在您投入生产时，
I think that's enough talking let's do
我认为谈话就足够了
what I think is the cool stuff and going
我认为很酷的东西
to do some hacking and I will I will
做一些黑客，我会
show you a map location let me just
显示地图位置让我
start it up it's not that in that in
启动它不是在那
that interesting the application itself
有趣的应用程序本身
let me look the demo application let me
让我看看演示应用程序
restart it just to be sure always break
重新启动它，以确保始终会中断
the Democrats first to make sure that
民主党首先要确保
your downloads are working I ran
您的下载正常运行
everything on my local or local machine
我的本地或本地计算机上的所有内容
just to make sure that we do not have
只是为了确保我们没有
that much of interference so I've got a
这么多的干扰，所以我有一个
very good application and it's very nice
很好的应用程序，非常好
because well you see I'm a good good
因为好吧，你知道我很好
person in UX right I can do bootstrap
UX用户，我可以进行引导
basically it's a pretty simple app I
基本上这是一个非常简单的应用程序
have to look in I'm I can do I can post
一定要看，我可以，我可以张贴
messages over so in this case I'm
消息结束，所以在这种情况下，我
registering myself as Brian and I give
将自己注册为Brian，我给
myself a password cool and I submit okay
我自己的密码很酷，我可以提交
so now I'm in a mess debauch and the
所以现在我陷入混乱中，
administrator already put in a few
管理员已经放了一些
messages and so I can say yeah hello
消息，所以我可以说是
brains and I can't put something in is
脑子，我不能放东西
everything okay
一切都好
well this is okay and this works fine
好吧，这还可以，这很好
and it is cool this application has a
而且很酷，这个应用程序有一个
little bit of authentication and
一点认证和
authorization by using it token I will
通过使用令牌进行授权，我将
show that right away that in the
立即显示
application we have a token over and
应用程序，我们有一个令牌
this token all it's basically it's not a
这个令牌，基本上不是
token that lifts short what normally you
代币通常会缩短您的寿命
should do but for the matter of for the
应该做，但是对于
sake of argument this token is that you
为了争辩这个令牌是你
identify yourself in efforts as long as
只要努力，就能证明自己
I have this token I am Brian and I can
我有这个令牌，我是Brian，我可以
and I can post it view but there's
我可以发布视图，但是
another thing we can do we can first of
我们可以做的另一件事是
all we have a awesome about page which
我们所有关于页面的信息都很棒
says everything about is this
说关于这一切
application that is the most amazing
最神奇的应用
about page and we can for some reason we
关于页面，由于某种原因，我们可以
can upload files over and what we can do
可以上传文件以及我们可以做什么
over here we can upload just not not
在这里我们可以上传不是
just upload files we can upload zip
只需上传文件，我们就可以上传zip
files and it will automatically unzip
文件，它将自动解压缩
that sounds really cool what we going to
听起来真的很酷，我们要做的是
do is we going I know don't know why I
我们要去吗我知道不知道为什么
know that there is a vulnerability over
知道存在漏洞
there and we're going to create a
在那里，我们将创建一个
vulnerable zip file what I'm going to do
易受攻击的zip文件，我要做什么
is and we'll show you the code about the
是，我们将向您展示有关
zip file simulator creator and I hope
zip文件模拟器的创建者，我希望
everybody can see that I'm going all
每个人都可以看到我要走了
large it a bit what I'm going to do is
大一点，我要做的是
I'm going to create a zip file core
我将创建一个zip文件核心
JetBrains demo zip and it contains two
JetBrains演示zip，其中包含两个
things
东西
it contains a text file with the body of
它包含一个文本文件，其正文为
there's a good text file and it contains
有一个很好的文本文件，其中包含
another file which is the about page dot
另一个文件是关于页面点
HTML
的HTML
well I'm trying I am going to create the
好吧，我正在尝试创建
about page PhD now I'm going to do is
我现在要做的是关于页面博士
uncork or going to do some path
开瓶器或要走一些路
traversal over here normally the zip
通常在这里遍历拉链
file will be downloaded or will be
文件将被下载或将
extracted in a certain file in
提取到某个文件中
public items file or something like that
公共项目文件或类似的东西
and I'm going to backtrack out of this
我要回溯一下
thing or I'm going to try to do that and
事情，或者我将尝试做到这一点，
override the about page in my in my
覆盖我的“我”中的“关于”页面
system so what I need to do I need to
系统，所以我需要做的是
add the content of that about page so
添加关于页面的内容，以便
let's go to the about page I'm going to
让我们转到我要去的关于页面
inspect that one and then we can get the
检查那个，然后我们可以得到
source I don't really care what have
来源我真的不在乎什么
what's happening here I just copy and
这里发生了什么，我只是复制并
paste it copy it and you see I going for
粘贴它复制它，你看到我要
the content and it got an evil book text
内容，并得到一本邪恶的书本
open evil Oh texting you see a little
打开邪恶哦发短信你看到一点
script oh they let me just first put the
脚本哦，他们让我先放
HTML over here and make sure that the
此处的HTML，并确保
script is part of the HTML and now I
脚本是HTML的一部分，现在我
have to end it with like this cool now
现在必须以这样酷的结尾
what you see over here is that I just
你在这里看到的是，我只是
inside I just recreated the same HTML
里面我只是重新创建了相同的HTML
page and just to show you that it's a
页，只是为了向您展示这是一个
different I will put a dot behind it so
不一样，我会在它后面加一个点
that if we override it then you can see
如果我们覆盖它，那么您可以看到
that it happens and I insert some some
它发生了，我插入一些
malicious JavaScript idea with a
带有
JavaScript I will get or grab the cookie
JavaScript我将获取或获取Cookie
and I will look what cookie you have and
我会看看你有什么饼干
I send that cookie to another URL and
我将该Cookie发送到另一个网址，
what is not URL does I will show you
什么不是网址，我会告诉你
right now if I have a good thing like
如果我现在有个好东西
over here and I give it to tell you hi
在这里，我给你打个招呼
Tricia then it gives me the hi Tricia
特里西娅然后它给了我喜特里西娅
back but if I look into this little
回来，但如果我看着这点
application I have it this is my help
应用程序有它这是我的帮助
browser and then you see its items then
浏览器，然后您会看到其项目
you see that this hi Tricia is safe
你看这个喜翠西亚很安全
daily so if I can save you any text over
每天，所以如果我能帮您保存任何文字
here that I just give to the parameter
在这里，我只是给参数
of this URL that is cool just to see
只是很酷的URL
some things but what I'm trying to do
有些事情，但我想做的是
here in this thing is getting your
这件事在这里让你
cookie and try to store that cookie with
cookie并尝试使用存储该cookie
that service so just redirect it to
该服务，因此只需将其重定向到
another URL so I can just steal your
另一个网址，这样我就可以窃取您的
token well having said that I want to do
说完我想做的事
this I love
这个我爱
just created used zip file and by doing
刚刚创建了使用的zip文件，并通过
so you will see over here that I just
所以你会看到我在这里
created this zip file cool let's go back
创建了这个zip文件，很酷，让我们返回
into the application I will go into I'm
进入应用程序，我将进入
still Brian and I'm uploading this file
还是布莱恩，我正在上传这个文件
doesn't matter who uploads it because
谁上传都没关系，因为
we're going we're going to overwrite
我们要覆盖
stuff so I'm going to upload this
东西，所以我要上传这个
JetBrains demo we just created oh let me
我们刚刚创建的JetBrains演示哦，让我
just show you that it's really a zip
只是告诉你这真的是一个拉链
file if I go into the terminal over here
如果我进入这里的终端文件
and I see that my jet range demo zip is
我看到我的喷气机范围演示zip是
over here and if we look at the zip info
在这里，如果我们查看邮政编码信息
of this zip file then you see that it
该zip文件的内容，然后您会看到它
contains a good or text and a weird HTML
包含一个很好的文本或一个奇怪的HTML
file with some dot dot slash in it so
文件中带有一些点点斜杠，因此
going to my browser I will pick up this
转到我的浏览器，我将接起这个
zip open it and I submit it and what we
zip打开它，我提交它，然后我们
see over here is that we have no errors
看到这里是我们没有错误
and we see that the good text that I
我们看到我的好文字
also put in was unpacked and displayed
也放进去包装并展示
over here and it is this place the
在这里，就是这个地方
target for the directory where the
目标目录
things supposed to be going so that
事情本来应该这样
might mean that the other part of the
可能意味着
zip file the dots lifepod the about HTML
zip文件点lifepod关于HTML
is also unpacked and does some pattern a
也被解压缩并做了一些模式
does some maybe does some pack traversal
做一些也许做一些包装遍历
and maybe means that the about page
也许意味着关于页面
contains that dot but also means that my
包含该点，但也意味着我的
cookie was read from my browser and was
cookie是从我的浏览器中读取的，
sent to my other servers over here so if
发送到我的其他服务器在这里，如果
I just read were a rerun that items then
我刚才读的是重新运行的那个项目
you see that I now have a token you see
你看到我现在有一个令牌
this a
这是
this is the one I can now use so let me
这是我现在可以使用的一个，让我
put that on my clipboard let me open her
把它放在我的剪贴板上让我打开她
a new browser and go to the localhost
一个新的浏览器，然后转到本地主机
let me simply just to make sure that it
让我只是为了确保它
works let me login and now I am user foo
作品让我登录，现在我是用户foo
I you see but by going to my application
我看到了，但是转到我的应用程序
cookies deleting this inserting this one
Cookie删除此插入此
I just stole cool let me try again now
我只是偷了酷，让我现在再试一次
certainly I'm Brian that means that from
当然，我是Brian，这意味着
this other browser I stole your token
这个其他浏览器我偷了你的令牌
and I can now take over your session of
现在我可以接管您的
course this website is not really secure
当然这个网站不是很安全
the token is not a long-lived token and
该令牌不是长期令牌，并且
etc etc but you see how easy it is if a
等等等等，但是你会发现如果一个
zip file is not properly constructed and
zip文件未正确构建，并且
on the other side it's not properly
另一方面，这是不正确的
unzipped so you see that I just stole
解压缩，所以你看到我偷了
your thing and I can do much more and if
你的事情，我可以做得更多，如果
I go to the other web page normal ones
我去其他网页正常
over here and I go to messages you see
在这里，我去看你看到的消息
that I didn't type this but the other PD
我没有打这个，但另一个PD
are the other person that sold my token
是卖我代币的另一个人
did well that's about the hacking part
做得好，这是关于黑客攻击的部分
but now we're going to look into the
但是现在我们将研究
problem part so going into your IDE in
问题部分，所以进入您的IDE
this case well I first go and show you
这样的话我先去给你看
where the problem is and we can do this
问题出在哪里，我们可以做到这一点
in a certain amount of waste because for
在一定数量的浪费，因为
the unzipping part I'm using a library
我正在使用库的解压缩部分
if I'm going to my maven problem it will
如果我要去解决Maven问题，它将
see I will do you use this CD zip
看到我会用这个CD zip吗
library but well I just got this from
图书馆，但是我刚从
the internet for amazing central where
互联网上令人惊叹的中央
whenever ago I just put it in and it
每当我把它放进去
works so how can we
工作，所以我们怎么能
find out that something is vulnerable
找出一些易受伤害的东西
because as a developer I want to know if
因为作为开发人员，我想知道
I'm vulnerable and what is vulnerable
我很脆弱，什么脆弱
and if I can solve it because if I can
如果我可以解决，因为如果可以
can solve it in my on my local machine
可以在我的本地机器上解决
then it will be so much more great then
那就好多了
at the end of the line because then I
在行的结尾，因为那时我
have to maybe have to do some rework
可能不得不做一些返工
maybe things cannot be used so I have to
也许事情无法使用，所以我不得不
so you look for another package and if I
所以你寻找另一个包裹，如果我
can look it up now and see if a package
现在可以查一下，看看有没有包装
is already vulnerable or not then it
已经脆弱或不是脆弱
might save me a lot of time so we can do
可能会节省我很多时间，所以我们可以
that in a few ways I've installed the
我以几种方式安装了
sneak tooling on this machine and I
在这台机器上偷偷摸摸的工具，我
don't insult the sneak CLI and we can
不要侮辱潜行CLI，我们可以
use it for my terminal and well although
用它为我的终端，虽然
you can use your terminal the one over
你可以使用你的终端一
here you can also use your terminal over
在这里您还可以使用终端
here so here I'm already in the correct
在这里，所以在这里我已经正确了
part and I'm simply calling sneak test
部分，我只是打电话给潜行测试
it's it it is as easy as that
就是那样简单
and what you see is that from this point
从这一点上你看到的是
it will analyze your maven dependency
它将分析您的Maven依赖关系
tree it will create yeah it will create
树，它将创建是，它将创建
a tree for you and it sends the tree
一棵树给你，它发送树
over to the sneaked online system and
进入潜行的在线系统，
what the sneaked online system does it
偷偷摸摸的在线系统做了什么
simply looks at your dependency tree and
只是看你的依赖树，
see which the fantasy you use and which
看你用哪个幻想和哪个幻想
transit dependencies they have and if
他们有过境依赖，如果
there are vulnerabilities in there so
那里有漏洞，所以
and I see over here that I have this CT
我在这里看到我有这个CT
zip file and it has a problem well let
压缩文件，它有一个问题，让
me see what the problem is by going to
我去看看问题是什么
the website you will get information
您将获得信息的网站
about a certain exploit and you see what
关于某个漏洞利用，您会看到
the problem is and you see which
问题是，你看到哪个
versions are vulnerable and which not
版本易受攻击，而哪些不易受攻击
and you see on the website that it's
然后您在网站上看到
something with 113 instead it then and
用113代替它然后
it might be ok so it gives you
可能还可以，所以可以给您
information how important this is or not
信息这有多重要
this one is just a medium severity going
这只是中等严重程度
back to my my terminal of here it also
回到我在这里的终端
gives me a remediation advice and it
给我一个修复建议，它
says that by not using 12 but using 13
说不使用12但使用13
1.13 it will solve the problem but this
1.13它将解决问题，但这
is from your terminal and it can be
来自您的终端，它可以是
nicer and as someone some other things
和其他人一样好
in this case CLI also scan
在这种情况下，CLI也会扫描
for licensing problems but what we also
对于许可问题，但我们还
have is we created something for the
我们为我们创造了一些东西
actual vulnerabilities not for licensing
不用于许可的实际漏洞
from for the vulnerabilities we created
来自我们创建的漏洞
a plug-in for IntelliJ and if that
IntelliJ的插件，如果有的话
plug-in works with maven so for the
插件可与Maven一起使用，因此对于
questions it does it also work with
问题它也可以使用
Gretl not yet we're working on that one
Gretl还不是我们正在研究的那个
that is on our backlog but just to show
那是我们的积压，但只是为了显示
you how easy it is if you're using maven
你在使用Maven时有多容易
and we see when we see that still from
我们看到当我们仍然从
the JVM report last year we still we see
去年的JVM报告我们仍然看到
that maven is still the the greatest one
那位专家仍然是最伟大的
or the biggest the largest used package
或最大，最大的二手包装
managing or dependency management
管理或依赖管理
management system if I open my main
管理系统，如果我打开我的主
thing over here and I opened the snick
事情在这里，我打开了尼克
plugin AV him then I can and I just well
插件AV他然后我可以，我很好
let me be sure that it works over here
让我确定它可以在这里工作
and you see that we have two real
你会看到我们有两个真实的
vulnerabilities and that's a
漏洞，这是一个
vulnerability of my h2 database which I
我的h2数据库的漏洞
use just for demo purposes and it's that
仅用于演示目的，就是这样
zero turnaround problem or both of these
零周转问题或两者兼而有之
problems are top-level dependencies and
问题是顶级依赖关系
so this is quite easy but say for
所以这很容易，但是要说
instance I would be using a 2.0 does and
实例，我将使用2.0并
it just won't work because I have not -
这只是行不通，因为我没有-
yes ok so you now you see that I'm using
是的，好的，所以您现在您看到我正在使用
and all the spring version and you see
还有所有春季版本，您会看到
that we have much more problems for
我们还有更多的问题
instance over here it's something with
实例在这里与
the fastest ml Jetson thingy and by
最快的毫升Jetson
opening it you will see where the actual
打开它，您将看到实际的位置
problem is it's not in the spring would
问题是不是在春天会
start a date arrest but the spring would
开始约会，但春天会
start to JSON and by updating it to
开始使用JSON并将其更新为
another version it will help you out and
另一个版本，它将帮助您
that that version that we just show you
我们刚刚向您展示的那个版本
over here doesn't have that
这边没有那个
vulnerability anymore but let me go back
漏洞了，但让我回头
and you can go up and down with that and
然后你可以上下移动
you see that we have that for many other
你会看到我们还有其他
things right so okay that's - I'm going
正确的事情就这样-我要
to go back to my original one
回到我原来的
not five release it over here and you
没有五个人在这里释放它，而你
see they only have to fondle bilities
看到他们只需要抚养能力
left by clicking on it I will go
单击它离开我会去
directly into my palm file to the right
直接放入右边的我的手掌锉
declaration and I see okay it's 1 or 12
声明，我知道是1或12
and by doing the 1.30 and again yes you
并通过执行1.30再一次是
can also I could who could also do the
我也可以谁也可以
auto imports but I choose not to because
自动导入，但我选择不这样做，因为
normally I work with large available
通常我会大量工作
parts and it can take a while and I only
零件，可能需要一段时间，而我只是
and now I see I fixed it funner ability
现在我看到我修复了它的取笑功能
by simply putting in another Nimmi I
通过简单地放入另一个Nimmi我
only have this h2 left over here so I'm
这里只有这个h2剩下，所以我
going to restart this demo so by killing
要重启这个演示，所以通过杀死
this one and running my name my
这个和我的名字我的
application once again the application
再次申请
is up once again creating the zip file
再次创建了zip文件
because well I automatically clean it up
因为好吧，我会自动清理它
because I do not want you to end up with
因为我不希望你以
that much fuzzy if I want you to redo
如果我要你重做那么模糊
the demo but by running this zip creator
演示，但运行此zip创建器
again and we here again have that jet
再次，我们在这里再次拥有那架喷气机
bench camera zip which just to prove
台式相机拉链只是为了证明
that it's real it has that about page so
这是真的，它与页面有关
I'm going to go we're going to do the
我要去，我们要去做
same thing again so going back here and
同样的事情，所以回到这里，
to do the h80 pod well have to login or
要做好h80吊舱，必须先登录或
register myself register my NX Brian
注册自己注册我的NX Brian
because well I using an h2 database so
因为我使用的是H2数据库
everything is gone no I do not want to
一切都消失了不，我不想
say that and I can do messages again
这样说，我可以再次发送消息
perfect that works I'm going to upload
完美的作品，我要上传
that file again the same vulnerable file
该文件再次成为易受攻击的文件
I open it and I submit and I see I have
我打开它，提交并看到
a wide label error page and if you see
宽标签错误页面，如果您看到
in there
在那里
bottom line you see that the file dot
底线，您看到文件点
dot slash dot dot slash target is trying
点斜杠点斜杠目标正在尝试
to leave the target ID with directory of
将目标ID保留在目录为
the public upload and we are ignoring
公开上传，我们忽略了
this form so okay that means that if I'm
这种形式很好，这意味着如果我
going back to my home page going back to
回到我的主页回到
the files that the good or text is there
有商品或文字的文件
but the about page it's without the dot
但是关于页面没有点
and to inspect the HTML we will see it
并检查HTML，我们将看到它
does not contain that malicious
不包含恶意
JavaScript on the bottom so what we see
底部的JavaScript，所以我们看到了
over here is that by just using another
在这里是通过使用另一个
package and making sure that I can do
包装并确保我可以做
that from my local machine I can save my
从我的本地计算机上，我可以保存我的
team and the rest of the world maybe
团队和世界其他地方
from a lot of harm and that's what we
受到很多伤害，这就是我们
mean by shifting security left is that
左移安全性的意思是
we want to be able to do this from the
我们希望能够从
perspective of a developer so you want
开发人员的角度，所以你想要
to provide you with tools to help you
为您提供帮助您的工具
out not just you point out that
不仅仅是你指出
something is vulnerable or not but also
有些东西是脆弱的还是不是
how to fix it or how to make it less
如何解决或减少它
vulnerable and then it's up to you how
脆弱，然后由您决定如何
to do that if it's a vulnerability that
如果这是一个漏洞
is not that major or it's not applicable
不是主要的还是不适用的
to you then your you can choose to
给你，那么你可以选择
ignore it but if it is if it's a
忽略它，但是如果它是一个
vulnerability that you might think that
您可能认为的漏洞
ok did can this can be this can be awful
好的，这可以吗，这可能会很糟糕
that we can you can fix it well in a
我们可以将其修复得很好
blink of an eye and if I can do it now
眨眼，如果我现在能做
and now push it to my to my master repo
现在将其推送给我的主存储库
instead of pushing a vulnerable library
而不是推一个脆弱的图书馆
at this point and not and only catching
在这一点上，并不仅如此
it at the end we save ourselves a lot of
最后，我们为自己节省了很多
times because it doesn't have to go that
时代，因为它不必走那
whole cycle from up and down from it's
从上到下的整个周期
here and I don't have to wait on my CI
在这里，我不必等待我的CI
system to point out that we have a
系统指出我们有一个
problem and I can do that before
问题，我可以做到这一点
something happens so actually what we
发生了什么，所以实际上我们
want to do over here is we want to solve
想在这里做的是我们要解决的
problems right
正确的问题
so if we look at a solution for this we
因此，如果我们为此寻求解决方案，
think that it's about three things team
认为这是团队的三件事
culture process and tooling and these
文化过程和工具，以及这些
things are equally important because the
事情同样重要，因为
tooling can be great but if it doesn't
工具可能很棒，但如果不是这样
fit your Church in culture or your
使您的教会适应文化或
process it will be doomed so if we look
处理将注定要失败，所以如果我们看一下
at that weird if we look at team cold
如果我们看团队感到冷漠
ship we have to look at the point where
船，我们必须看点
do what do people care about
做人们关心的事情
well developers we care about creating
好我们关心的开发人员
new stuff putting his new stuff as fast
新事物将他的新事物放得快
as possible into our products and move
尽可能地融入我们的产品并移动
on to the next cool thing you want to
转到您想要的下一件酷事
create right so we want to create things
创造权利，所以我们要创造事物
only once you make it work we want to
只有您使它起作用，我们才想
build things that's what we and I
建立我们和我的东西
consider myself still developer although
认为自己仍然是开发人员
I'm a developer advocate we want to make
我是我们想做的开发者拥护者
things the security team most of the
安全团队的大部分事情
time doesn't care about if it works or
时间不在乎是否可行，或者
not because if it doesn't work it will
不是因为如果它不起作用
not go to production they do not have to
不去生产，他们不必
care about security issues so they have
关心安全问题，这样他们就可以
a very I have another point of view in
我非常有另一种观点
it
它
the only thing they think about it the
他们唯一想到的是
only thing they care about it is not
他们唯一关心的不是
being vulnerable not being hacked not
容易受到攻击
being exploited and that the data of the
被利用，并且
customers is safe operations people they
客户是他们的安全运营人
think about maintainability how can we
考虑可维护性
easily maintain this system can I just
轻松维护这个系统
push a button and reset the the service
按下按钮并重置服务
can I just redeploy that stuff so it
我可以重新部署这些东西吗
will be it will be maybe even
可能会甚至
self-healing or something like that and
自我修复之类的
if it's if a developer cannot make it
如果开发人员无法做到这一点
work well it doesn't go into production
运行良好，无法投入生产
and operation doesn't and have to
而且操作没有，而且必须
maintain it they do not care about if
维护它，他们不在乎
it's secure or not they just their job
这是安全的还是不是他们的工作
is to me change stuff and management
对我来说是改变东西和管理
well I could say I could make it at ease
好吧，我可以说我可以放心
if management care about cares about
管理层是否关心
money but they care about profitability
钱，但他们关心获利能力
making making it profitable and making
使它有利可图
sure that you as a company are still in
确保您作为公司还在
the lead if you compare that to your
如果您将其与您的铅进行比较
competitors so if we can align this and
竞争对手，所以如果我们能做到这一点，
if we can see that the security is part
如果我们看到安全是其中的一部分
of everybody's job and take it back to
每个人的工作，并带回去
ourselves
我们自己
first because what we can change we
首先，因为我们可以改变我们
cannot change other people but we can do
不能改变别人，但是我们可以做
can change ourselves if we can take that
可以改变自己，只要我们能够接受
up to developers then we still have to
由开发人员决定，那么我们仍然必须
put it into our process right so process
将其放入我们的流程中，以便流程
is a bit of a hustle because nobody
有点忙，因为没人
wants to change in general some people
想改变一些人
might want to change but not really if I
可能想改变，但如果我不是真的
create a super new cool process around
在周围创造一个超级酷的过程
things people are not used to that
人们不习惯的事情
people will make mistakes in a proto
人们会在原型中犯错
process or people just don't care and if
过程或人们只是不在乎，如果
I if we can use your current process
如果我们可以使用您当前的流程
which works and the people are familiar
哪个有效并且人们熟悉
with and just make the new practices
并进行新的实践
work in that process that's already
在已经完成的过程中工作
working for you then you might have a
为你工作，那么你可能会有一个
chance if we want to create more process
如果我们想创建更多流程的机会
we will end up doing this for two weeks
我们将这样做两个星期
and then back to normal right
然后恢复正常
so then the tooling the tooling should
所以工具应该
support your process so we had you have
支持您的流程，以便我们拥有您
to pick tooling that is there and works
选择在那里工作的工具
for you well that's why I showed you
对你来说这就是为什么我向你展示
that you can do this from your local
您可以从本地进行
machine so you're not only waiting for
机器，所以您不仅在等待
at the end but we you can now do this
最后，但我们现在可以执行此操作
while you are developing inside your
当你在内部发展时
your ie or if you're more of a terminal
您的ie，或者如果您更像一个终端
person like me you can use it for from
像我这样的人，您可以将其用于
the from the from the terminal if you
来自终端的，如果您
use the rest of our snakes tag you can
使用我们其余的蛇标签，您可以
connect your repository to our scanning
将您的存储库连接到我们的扫描
capabilities as well so every time a new
以及每次新功能
pull requests come in we can scan it for
拉入请求，我们可以对其进行扫描
you every time or and and we can scan it
您每次或，我们可以对其进行扫描
on a daily basis for you because well
每天为您服务，因为
vulnerabilities takes time to be found
漏洞需要时间才能被发现
and the fun part is that you can do that
而有趣的是，您可以做到这一点
integrate it into your CI system still
仍将其集成到您的CI系统中
because well that is still needed the
因为那仍然需要
gatekeeper but not just as the only part
看门人，但不仅是唯一的一部分
and then you're not done because once it
然后你就没有做完，因为一旦完成
is it is in production we still need to
是否在生产中，我们仍然需要
scan and we can do that either from our
扫描，我们可以从我们的
local system or
本地系统或
from our CI system but if I just do over
从我们的CI系统中获取，但如果我只是结束
here from the terminal instead of sneak
从航站楼这里而不是潜行
test what I already ate and I do sneak
测试我已经吃了，然后偷偷摸摸
monitor what you see is that it will
监视您看到的是它将
create a dependency a tree again from
再次从中创建依赖关系树
the local system and it posts that
本地系统并将其发布
snapshot to the website and by going to
快照到网站，并转到
this URL you will see that I have a few
这个网址，您会看到我有一些
problems with licensing but and I have
许可问题，但我有
that the thing with the h2 database and
与H2数据库有关的东西
now you can scan it on a daily basis so
现在您可以每天对其进行扫描，因此
when you go to production take that
当你投入生产时
snapshot put it up to put it up in the
快照将其放入
air
空气
only the we only take we only take a
只有我们只采取我们只采取
look at your dependency tree not your
看你的依赖树而不是你的
code because well as I say we do not
代码，因为正如我所说，我们不
care about your code or we cannot say
在乎您的代码，否则我们无法说
anything about your code without any
关于您的代码的任何内容
context but we can scan your
上下文，但我们可以扫描您的
dependencies that you know that the
你知道的依赖
things you trust on or you use even if
您信任或使用的东西，即使
they are in production you can be
他们正在生产中，你可以
alerted and not actively looking for new
受到警告，没有积极寻找新的
vulnerabilities but let's our system or
漏洞，但让我们的系统还是
any system alert you so at the end what
任何系统都会提醒您，最后
we want what we are trying to say is
我们想要我们要说的是
shift security left make sure that you
向左转移安全性，确保您
start on the left side you start on your
从左侧开始，从开始
local machine do it in all the other
本地机器在其他所有地方都做
passes within your development cycle in
在您的开发周期内通过
your master branch or scan your scan
您的主分支或扫描您的扫描
your git repository scan your new
您的git存储库扫描您的新
request and scan while doing it on your
请求并扫描，同时在您的
see Isis inside of your CI built and
在您的CI中查看Isis，并
also scan where your in production but
还扫描您的生产位置，但是
you have to start at the far left and
你必须从最左边开始
that's most of time it's us at the local
大多数时候是我们在当地
machines at your IDE and that's why we
您的IDE上的计算机，这就是为什么我们
created the plugins and that's why we
创建了插件，这就是为什么我们
will maintain the plugins that we will
将维护我们将要使用的插件
expand the plugins with new capabilities
使用新功能扩展插件
for instance for for for a greater
例如为了更大
winner in a later stage and for now if
赢家在稍后阶段，如果现在
you for instance want to use Gretel
例如您要使用Gretel
instead of maven
代替行家
you can do that by using the CLI so the
您可以通过使用CLI做到这一点，因此
the terminal the common line tool that
终端通用线工具
that supports Gradle only the the
仅支持Gradle的
plug-in ie that but you see how nice it
插件即那个，但是你看到它很好
is if you can do this from our system
如果您可以从我们的系统中执行此操作
and just by a single click go to the
只需单击一下，转到
vulnerable application order founder of
易受攻击的应用程序订单的创建者
all part I fix it I'm ending here well
我修复的所有部分我都在这里结束了
you see my email and my Twitter handle
您会看到我的电子邮件和Twitter句柄
if you have questions afterwards on the
如果您以后对
right side of your screen you will see a
在屏幕的右侧，您会看到一个
well a very 1980 QR code now with a link
现在有一个非常1980年的QR码，带有链接
below that and that link is about the
在那下面，那个链接是关于
new JVM survey we just put out and I
我们刚刚发布的新JVM调查
want to ask everybody who working on
想问每个人谁在做
Java or any jvm language to fill in that
Java或任何jvm语言来填写
server to give not only us but we will
服务器不仅要给我们，还要给我们
publish it we will publish the results
发布它，我们将发布结果
anyway to give us a better view on how
无论如何让我们更好地了解
the whole JVM ecosystem and landscape
整个JVM生态系统和格局
works work together with the major
与专业合作
conferences within the Java world so as
Java世界范围内的会议
devoxx and dive nexus and jay focus and
devoxx和潜水关系和jay重点以及
all these these guys album is out as
这些家伙的专辑都出来了
well and the more info we have the more
好，我们拥有的信息越多
we can help developers out because
我们可以帮助开发人员，因为
that's basically what we're trying to do
这基本上就是我们想要做的
and well that's the end of the stuff I
这就是我的工作的终点
prepared for this webinar so are there
为此网络研讨会做准备，在那里
any questions Trisha and that was great
任何问题特丽莎，那太好了
thank you I found it kind of scary scary
谢谢，我觉得有点吓人
how easy it is to sometimes a to hack
有时候入侵是多么容易
into other people's sessions and
参加其他人的会议
manipulate things and we did have a few
操纵东西，我们确实有一些
questions you mostly answered them
您主要回答他们的问题
during the session so we had a question
在会议期间，我们有一个问题
about what does it work for Gradle which
关于它对Gradle有什么作用
he said that the Gradle stuff is a work
他说Gradle的东西是一件工作
in progress this is for the plug-in
正在进行中，用于插件
right yeah the Gradle is the greater
是的，Gradle更大
part is working progress for the plug-in
部分是插件的工作进度
it does we have the scanning
我们有扫描吗
capabilities already in our system in
我们系统中已有的功能
our online system and India in ECL I so
我们的在线系统和ECL中的印度
if you just use sneak tests in your
如果你只是在你的偷偷摸摸的测试
truck for a magic terminal or magic
魔术终端或魔术卡车
terminal within you within IntelliJ
IntelliJ中您内部的终端
you already get results on Gretel
您已经在Gretel上获得了结果
so I works but it doesn't but it doesn't
所以我工作，但是没有，但是没有
work yet in the in the in the plugin we
在插件中我们还可以工作
working in the program for the ide i'm
在程序中为我工作
any i've been asked about if there's a
我被问到是否有一个
timeline for that but i know they're
时间表，但我知道他们
asking for estimates is always a tricky
要求估价总是很棘手的
thing
事情
yeah i will not give us the midst on
是的，我不会给我们
that because i'm not the only one
那是因为我不是唯一的一个
working on that and there we support a
为此，我们支持
lot of ecosystems
很多生态系统
we try to make it as soon as possible
我们试图尽快做到
but in the meantime we're also doing
但与此同时，我们也在做
plugins for other things for other other
其他东西的插件
i des for other others i'm sorry i'm
我为其他人而战我对不起
sorry but we also first the first first
对不起，但我们也是第一第一
video first we did the implementation of
视频首先我们做了实施
the plugin for teamcity to make sure
teamcity的插件，以确保
that we work with one of the greatest
我们与最伟大的人之一合作
EAJA systems and this one was the first
EAJA系统，这是第一个
actually so this was first and after
实际上，这是第一次和之后
that the rest came and yes we're working
剩下的来了，是的，我们正在努力
on that I'm not giving you can give you
我不给你可以给你
any timeline on that but it's very high
任何时间表，但都很高
on our backlog that's the only thing I
在我们的积压订单中，这是我唯一的事情
can say yeah fair enough and if the
可以说是足够公平，如果
support is already there in the CLI it's
支持已经在CLI中了
not like it can't be done for Gradle
不喜欢Gradle无法完成
it's just it can't be done through the
只是无法通过
through the IDE plug-in specifically and
通过专门的IDE插件
you mentioned that city plug-in there so
您提到那里有城市插件
I think that's an interesting part too I
我也觉得这很有趣
mean having it in the IDE is really
意味着在IDE中拥有它确实
useful for developers but having it's
对开发人员很有用，但拥有它
part of your continuous integration
持续集成的一部分
pipeline is it's also probably even more
管道也可能更多
important because you want to be able to
重要，因为您希望能够
catch it at a more centralized place
在更集中的地方抓
than then necessary just relying on each
那就需要依靠每个
individual developer right I think you
个人开发者权利，我想你
have to do both so if you do it on your
都必须这样做，所以如果您在自己的计算机上执行此操作
develop on your developer machine she
她在您的开发人员机器上进行开发
will not get new stur new new problems
不会得到新的新的新问题
in but you still have to do it into your
在，但您仍然必须将其放入您的
in your inside of your continuous
在你连续的内心
integration about pipeline because well
关于管道的整合，因为很好
you do not want to go to productions and
你不想去制作
by the time it leaves your machine into
等到机器离开时
until you are in your until you're
直到你进入你的
building it in and deploying it that can
建立并部署它可以
take a few while it maybe takes a weeks
可能要花几个星期
because well I didn't check in into the
因为好吧，我没有签入
master branch but did it on on a
主分支，但在
separate branch because I'm developing
单独的分支，因为我正在开发
something and at that point it was still
到那时，它仍然
good I post it and then we have that
好，我张贴它，然后我们得到
problem so we you have to do it I think
问题，所以我们必须这样做
you have to do it in all levels during
在此期间，您必须在各个层面上做到这一点
also all points with
还有所有要点
your development cycle so it's not just
您的开发周期，而不仅仅是
one or the other I think I but that's of
一个或另一个我想我但是那是
course I'm working for security company
我在保安公司工作
so it's preaching for your own choir
所以这是为你自己的合唱团传教
it's I think you have to do it in every
我认为您必须在每一个步骤中都做到这一点
step yeah if you wanna be safe with it
是的，如果你想安全的话
you if you want to be quick with it have
你如果你想快点有
at the developer level if you want to be
如果您想成为开发人员，
secure that it's being applied as a
确保将其作为
before it goes into production like you
在像您一样投入生产之前
say you needed at all points in the in
说您在任何时候都需要
the process and another question was do
这个过程，另一个问题是做
we need to install the CLI to use the
我们需要安装CLI才能使用
plug-in nope you don't if you you can
如果可以的话，您可以不使用插件
install the CLI but you do not have to
安装CLI，但是您不必
Anson CLI to use the plug-in what you
Anson CLI使用您所使用的插件
have to do to use the plug-in is to
使用插件要做的就是
download it from from a marketplace and
从市场上下载它，然后
you do have to connect it to a sneek
你必须将它连接到一个时髦
account and the state account is free
帐户和国家帐户是免费的
I'm not sure if you have to create an
我不确定您是否必须创建一个
account first or you can stick the
首先帐户，或者您可以坚持
create distinct account on the month
在当月创建不同的帐户
because well I have this thing on the
因为好吧，我在这件事上
plug-in on for ages and well why should
插件有很长一段时间了，为什么要这样
I and install it so I didn't try that
我安装它，所以我没有尝试
I'm not sure yet but we have to connect
我不确定，但我们必须连接
your snick account to to the plug-in and
您的昵称帐户即可访问该插件，
it will be a one-time job to do so and
这样做将是一次性的工作，并且
it's it's free are there any questions
有任何问题吗？
about that that kind of thing is it if
关于那种事情，如果
you can use it for free so I can make
您可以免费使用它，所以我可以
that a little bridge well there's a kind
有点桥，有一种
of related question with which was does
与之相关的问题
it work with the community version of
它与社区版本一起使用
IntelliJ IDEA as well as the ultimate
IntelliJ IDEA以及最终版本
version and I found from the
版本，我从
documentation it works with both
两者均可使用的文档
community and ultimate so yes free IDE
社区和终极版，所以是免费的IDE
and free sneek account yes and if you do
和免费的sneek帐户是，如果您这样做
open saw the free snick account has a
打开看到免费的尼克帐户有一个
few limitations because from the Free
很少的限制，因为来自免费
State account you can only do I think it
国家帐户，您只能这样做
was 200 tests a month but from if you if
每月要进行200次测试，但如果
you don't do that like two hundred times
你不会像两百次那样
consecutively you can run with it if you
您可以连续使用它，如果您
do this for if you do open source
如果您是开源的，请这样做
development so you're maintaining open
开发，因此您保持开放
source packages there will give you
源码包会给你
unlimited rest and you can do that from
无限休息，您可以从
from the from the from the free
从免费
community version of IntelliJ or you or
社区版本的IntelliJ或您或
the
的
the paid version it doesn't matter it
付费版本没关系
works for both okay another question
都适用于另一个问题
since we need sneak account how much of
因为我们需要一个偷偷摸摸的帐户
the local code is uploaded to the sneak
本地代码被上传到潜行
server zero zero just the dependencies
服务器零零仅依赖项
yeah we would create a dependency tree
是的，我们将创建一个依赖树
in a certain format and so basically the
以某种格式，所以基本上
package name and a and and a version
软件包名称，a和and版本
number and at that point we we can just
数字，那时我们可以
have you say that cross compare to our
你说那个十字架和我们相比吗
to our our proprietary vulnerability
我们专有的漏洞
database that is basically what we do
数据库基本上就是我们要做的
and then we can find out if if it's the
然后我们可以找出是否
top level or the the transitive
顶层或传递
dependency that caused the problem with
导致问题的依赖性
severe appears and what may be the
严重出现，可能是什么
solution is if there is a solution
解决方案是如果有解决方案
because for some packages there is not
因为对于某些软件包，没有
yet a solution and so nobody got we do
还没有解决方案，所以没人做
not we do not speak your code okay the
不，我们不会说您的代码好吗
response to that on the questions was
对问题的答复是
that's awesome okay I actually just
真的很棒，我只是
wanted to reiterate something else he
想重申他的其他话
said about the JVM server there I have I
说说我那里的JVM服务器
will be adding a link to the JVM server
将添加到JVM服务器的链接
that you're running from sneak in
你是从偷偷跑来的
annotating monthly this week because
这周每月注释一次，因为
like you were saying I think it's really
就像你在说我认为这是真的
interesting to gather feedback from a
收集来自
bunch of developers from different
一堆来自不同的开发人员
business domains different countries
不同国家的业务领域
different backgrounds about what's
关于什么的不同背景
happening in the JVM world so that you
发生在JVM世界中，以便您
know we can kind of everyone who builds
知道我们可以帮助所有建造的人
products are open-source software or
产品是开源软件或
whatever can see what real developers
什么都可以看到真正的开发者
are actually doing in the real world and
实际上是在现实世界中
tailor our products accordingly really
相应地量身定制我们的产品
so I highly recommend that people go in
所以我强烈建议人们进去
and fill in that survey because it's
并填写该调查，因为它是
really interesting for for anyone who
对于任何人来说真的很有趣
has a Java or JVM related product I
有Java或JVM相关产品
think so yet there doesn't look like
这么认为，但看起来好像
there's any more questions at the moment
目前还有其他问题
we're coming up to the top of the hour
我们快到了
anyways so I think at this point it
无论如何，所以我认为在这一点上
would be quite good to wrap up have you
把你包裹起来会很好
got any more closing comments or are we
还有更多结束语或我们
good to wrap up if you come up with
好，如果你想出总结
questions feel free to to ping me on
问题随时可以联系我
Twitter or send me an email and I will
Twitter或给我发送电子邮件，我会
be glad to answer them or redirect you
很高兴回答他们或重定向您
to the people that can actually answer a
给可以真正回答一个问题的人
certain turn insights so no we just want
某些转弯见解，所以我们不想要
to thank everybody for the job beginner
谢谢大家对工作的初学者
listening
倾听
great thank you so much Brian for coming
非常感谢Brian的到来
on and and giving this talk I must admit
继续进行这个演讲，我必须承认
I'm one of those developers who is a bit
我是那些有点
lazy around security and anything which
懒惰的安全和任何
kind of can can make my life easier
可以使我的生活更轻松
in the IDE and point to problems before
在IDE中并指出问题之前
they become real problems is is a
他们成为真正的问题是
lifesaver for someone like me so this
像我这样的人的救星
was super useful um as I mentioned
就像我提到的那样非常有用
before we will be putting the recording
在我们开始录音之前
on the IntelliJ IDEA blog at some point
在某个时候在IntelliJ IDEA博客上
in the next few days and you can always
在接下来的几天里，您可以随时
see recordings of previous webinars of
查看以前的网络研讨会录像
screencast etc on our on our YouTube
在我们的YouTube上进行截屏等
channel and thank you so much Brian for
频道，非常感谢Brian
coming in and presenting you're getting
进来展示你正在
a lot of great feedback on there on the
那里有很多关于
questions panel saying it was a great
问题小组说这很棒
talk thank you
说话谢谢
you
您